

# Jordi Altayó González

Electrical Engineer

I am a 22-year-old Electrical Engineering student passionate about technology. My career goal is to gain experience in all facets of Engineering and move towards Microelectronic Design. I am also a musician with interests in Art and Philosophy.

### Education

2012-2014 High School, Sagrada Família, Sabadell.

Technological modality. See diploma.

2014–2018 Electrical Engineering B.Sc, UPC-ETSETB, Barcelona.

Electronics track. 240 ECTS.

2018–2020 Embedded Systems M.Sc, KTH, Stockholm.

Embedded Electronics track. 120 ECTS

2002–2016 Musical Education, Professional Conservatory, Sabadell.

Main instrument: viola.

o Secondary instruments: piano and trombone.

o Others: composer and arranger.

## Experience

2014-present **Private teacher**.

Maths, Physics and Electronics teacher for high-shcool-level students.

2015-present Musician, Simfònica de Cobla i Corda de Catalunya, Girona.

Titular violist. Participated in various award-wining CD recordings such as Tossudament Llach, Cançó

d'Amor i de Guerra and The Very Best.

2015-present Musician, Eiron Quintet, Sabadell.

Founder and member of the group.

Feb-Jul 2018 **R&D Intern**, eSilicon, Barcelona.

Developement of a metric analysis tool for ASIC HLBs under PrimeTime and ICC2 environements as part of an internship and the Bachelor's Degree Thesis. This tool will allow designers to have a quick overview on all aspects of the block during the design process without the need to deepen into the design and potentially lose time by analyzing useless or redundant data. It will also provide reports with design changes proposals (ECO) to either facilitate timing clousure or reduce power consumtion.

# Courses, awards and recognitions

October 2015 Composition Contest, Professional Conservatory, Sabadell.

Jury award for the piece "Quartet de Tardor". See diploma.

October 2016 Innovate or Die<sup>†</sup>, LEINN, Barcelona.

Second place at the challange of Pyrum(R). See diploma.

October 2016 Composition Contest, Professional Conservatory, Sabadell.

Jury and public award for the piece "Petit Príncep". See diploma.

Doctor Pujades 5 - 08203 - Sabadell, Barcelona

☐ +34 695 758 519 • ☑ jordialtayo+cv@gmail.com • **in** jagjordi This is a living document. To obtain the latest version visit bit.ly/cv\_jag November 2016 **EBEC**<sup>†</sup>, *B.E.S.T.*, Barcelona.

Winner of the Regional edition. See diploma.

April 2017 **EBEC**<sup>†</sup>, B.E.S.T., Valladolid.

Finalist of the National edition. See diploma.

<sup>†</sup>EBEC stands for European B.E.S.T. (Board of European Students of Technology) Engineering Competition. It is a contest where participants are given 48 hours to solve a challenge by designing and building a functional prototype with the resources provided by the organizers.

Sept-Dec 2017 CBI Course, UPC & CERN, Barcelona & Geneva.

Operational methods for radiation inspection project. See dioploma.

March 2018 Hackathon Mobility, SEAT & CARNET, Barcelona.

First place at SEAT challange: Al for Mobility & Driving Experience. See prize and video.

# Languages

Spanish Native

Catalan Native

English C1 (IELTS) See certificate
French B2 (DELF) See certificate

## Personal Skills

#### Programming Languages

- Python
- MATLAB
- o C/C++
- VHDL
- ATEX
- Tcl/Tk
- Bash

#### Soft Skills

- Multidisciplinary team-work capabilities
- Excellent communication skills
- Ability to analyze and solve complex problems

#### Software

- o Altium Designer
- o Eagle
- o Altera Quartus II
- PrimeTime
- o ICC 2
- LabVIEW (CLAD)
- SolidWorks

#### Others

- Driving license
- o Own car

## **Projects**

December 2015 Ultrasound distance meter, UPC, Barcelona.

Project developed in a group of 4 engineers. Report can be downloaded here.

December 2016 Class D audio amplifier, UPC, Barcelona.

Project developed in a group of 4 engineers. Report can be downloaded here.

June 2017 Autonomous weather-related measurement adquisition system, UPC, Barcelona.

Project developed in a group of 2 engineers. Report can be downloaded here.

December 2017 CBI Course, UPC & CERN, Barcelona & Geneva.

Project developed in a student team of 2 engineers, 2 designers and 2 MBAs. Final dossier can be downloaded here.

June 2018 Bachelor's Thesis. eSilicon & UPC. Barcelona.

See Experience for Project details. Final score of 98% with Honors.